## KAMLESH K. NAGMOTE

Email: kamleshnagmote@gmail.com/kamleshnagmote@outlook.com Contact No: +91-9209183967 / 08668382813

## **OBJECTIVE**

To work efficiently and effectively as well as grow with a prestigious organization in the field of Electronics and Electrical Engineering so as to achieve self-realization and the accomplishment of organizational goals.

#### **HIGHLIGHTS**

J	Annual Maintenance Contract Maintenance planning for induastrial battery
	charger, Online UPS upto 140KVA, PLC.
J	Participation in tender process, generating new AMC, Estimating Tender and
	calculating cost to the company.
J	Providing Budgetary offer and its follow up.
J	Worked on different make of battery charger likes Chhabi Electricals Pvt.
	Ltd., HBL power Systems Ltd. etc.
J	Worked on various make of batteries likes HBL power Systems Ltd., Exide,
	AMCO, ACHHCO of different types like Nickel-cadmium, Lead Acid, Valve
	Regulated Lead Acid, SMF types.
J	Worked on various make of UPS like Hitachi Hi-Rel, Emerson etc.
J	Supervised Various PLC AMC work of Schneider, Ge-Fanuc, ABB etc.
J	Deputation of Engineers
J	Engineer Planning and Schedule design.
J	Organised
J	Time management
J	Detail Oriented

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

1. Currently working at "Dolphin Innovative Service" Akola as an "Senior Engineer; Services-Electrical Maintenance" from Aug 2016 to present.

## **CTC Details**

Current Salary: - ~3.27 LPA~2.55 LPA + House Rent Allowances (1BHK Flat +

Electric Bill + Flat Maintenance)

Expected Salary: - 4.00 LPA (Including All)

#### **Job Responsibilities**

- Responsible for generating new AMC's for UPS, Industrial Battery Charger, Batteries, PLC's etc.
- Responsible for participation in the **Tender Process** like Providing budgetary offer, generating enquiries, filling tenders of NTPC, MSPGCL, MSETCL, MPPGCL, UPRVUNL, RRVUNL, CSPGCL, Sugar Factories, Power Plants, Refineries, Petrochemical plants for UPS, Industrial Battery Charger, Batteries, PLC's AMC, Spares procurement, As n when services, supply etc.
- Taking follow up to the customer for budgetary offer and payment.
- J Filling OEM enquiries, Open Tender (three party tender), Quoting the items and responsible for getting the new contracts.
- As a senior engineer services and commercial with responsibilities of **Scheduling** various AMC, **Scheduling of service Engineer**, **Deputation of service Engineer**.
- Managed multiple large capital projects for timely completion within assigned budget.
- Adept of handling **multiple projects** simultaneously whether working independently or as part of team.
- Providing telephonic support to the customer.
- Providing rough Schematic according customers requirement for Battery Charger and battery bank, UPS etc.
- J Testing of PCBs, Connectors, Power Supplies and control circuits.
- Facilitation inspection and designing for new product supplies as well as entertaining customer with required technical of product.
- Participating in technical events for product branding and promotions.
- Monitoring and maintaining daily target as required in the various project and AMC's.
- Participating in product promotional activities to fulfil the target of achieving 40% growth.
  - 2. Worked at "HBL Power System Ltd." as a "Service Project Engineer" Mumbai on the Project of Reliance Industries Ltd Dahej, Gujarat in department of Services and management for AMC from Aug 2015 to Aug 2016.

#### <u>Job Responsibilities</u>

- As a Project Engineer Services handled maintenance of Chhabi make, HBL make, Masstek make Battery Charger and battery bank at **Reliance Industries Dahej** Gujarat.
- Leading team for 7 team members at RIL to carried out daily battery and battery charger PM.
- Responsibilities of preparing monthly AMC schedule for battery charger and battery bank.
- *Providing telephonic support for battery charger.*
- Installation and commissioning of new battery charger, and battery bank.
- Attending service call for battery charger and battery installation.
- Worked on various projects like IOCL Refineries, ONGC petro additions Ltd., Reliance Industries Ltd., Essar power, Suzuki Motors, Shreeram DCM,GNFC, Firmenich Aromatic product, Ambuja cement etc.
- Monitoring and maintaining daily target as required in the project.
- Testing and repairing of battery charger PCBs and circuits.
  - 3. Worked at "ARMO Electronics and Electricals" from Nagpur as an "Engineer" in R&D Department From Sept 2013 to July 2015.

## Job Responsibilities

- Joined as Graduate Engineer trainee in R&D department.
- J Testing and Designing of circuits, PCB and battery charger, voltage stabiliser, CVT, UPS.
- Panel Testing, Wiring, Load test of battery charger of various projects according to customer requirements and to improve efficiency.
- J Testing and creating standard inspection reports of manufactured product like battery chargers, servo stabilisers, CVT, UPS.
- Participated on various projects of MPPTCL, CSPTCL, MSETCL.

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

- Conscientious and mindful of All kind of Tender doc, tender process, Employee Scheduling etc.
- *Efficiency* predicted the faults of some components in projects (Device) this improved the accuracy and efficiency.

- ) Solely entrusted with the responsibility of performing the reliability tests for the product which was successfully executed.
- Joined the company as a graduate engineer trainee and was prompted to the Electronics Testing engineer in Jan 2014.
- ) Conscientious and mindful of all type of battery charger, UPS, PLC and most of battery bank.
- ) College topper in HSSC.

#### **SOFTWARE SKILLS**

**Programming Languages:** Introductory knowledge of C, C++.

**Operating Systems:** Windows XP,7,8,10.

**Documentation Tools:** MS-Offices.

## **ACADEMIC QUALIFICATION**

- Technically qualified as Bachelor of Engineering graduate in Electronics and Telecommunication field from PRMIT&R College Amravati University with 64.44% in 2012.
- Passed HSC from B R Jr. College with 77.50% in 2008.
- Passed SSC from LHST School with 70% in 2006.

#### PERSONAL DETAILS

Date of Birth: 26th Jan 1991

**Passport No.:** L1804890 Expiry Date: 14.05.2023

**Permanent Address:** At- Dindargaon, TQ-Narkhed, Dist- Nagpur, 441304.

Languages: Marathi, English, Hindi.

# Thanking You

## KAMLESH K. NAGMOTE